A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25
1958-1974
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
FA368
119.21 record cartons 91 standard record storage boxes.
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 25
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
This series is divided into 9 subseries:
Subseries 1 - Public Relations Files Subseries 2 - Latin American Mission Subseries 3 - Agency and Commission Reports Subseries 4 - Positions and Policy Papers Subseries 5 - Political and Election Analysis Files Subseries 6 - County Visits Subseries 7 - Recommendations to Fill U.S. Senate Seat Following Robert F. Kennedy's Assassination, 1968 Subseries 8 - Miscellaneous Subseries 9 - Statements and Press Releases
Scope and Contents note
The material in this series was created and maintained by Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller's Press Office. The series includes copies of press releases documenting his governmental and political activities and some background material used in the creation of the releases. Also included is a small collection of statistical analysis reports used by the Governor's office to gauge public opinion on various issues.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; Political campaigns -- United States; New York (State); International economic relations; International relations; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Human rights; Legislation -- New York (State); New York (N.Y.); International relations -- United States; Latin America; Civil service; Civil defense -- United States; Economics; Civil service -- New York (State); Arms control; Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Civil defense; Arms control -- United States; Public policy; Public relations; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Federal government -- United States; Government policy; Vice-Presidents -- United States; State governments -- United States; United States
- Public Relations File, 1; 59 Cubic Feet
  Arrangement note
  Subseries 1 is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents note
  This is a collection of press releases documenting the activities of the four Rockefeller Administrations (January 1, 1959 - December 18, 1973). The releases include announcements concerning appointments, new state programs, legislation initiated, signed or vetoed by the Governor, the Governor's reaction to major events, and other official statements and proclamations. Also included are complete transcripts and abbreviated summaries of the Governor's speeches, travel itineraries and schedules of appearances provided for the benefit of the press, and transcripts of Governor Rockefeller's Town Meetings. The Town Meetings were public forums designed to provide greater exposure for the Governor and his initiatives. They were held throughout the state in 1967, 1969, and 1972.
  An incomplete collection of press releases from Rockefeller's 1958 gubernatorial campaign is also included here. There are also press releases and speech transcripts from Rockefeller's campaigns for the Republican nomination in the presidential elections of 1960, 1964, and 1968.
  This file continues past Gov. Rockefeller's resignation December 18, 1973. The post-gubernatorial releases are transcripts of interviews, press conferences, and speeches. Topics covered during this period include the privately funded Commission on Critical Choices (of which he was the chairman), Watergate, and his appointment as vice president. The last press release in this series is dated October 16, 1974.
  The Public Relations Files is not an entirely complete collection of Governor Rockefeller's press releases. A subject index is available. While it, too, has been proven incomplete, it is usable.
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - August 24, 1958 - April 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - April 26, 1959 - October 4, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - October 5, 1959 - December 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - December 15, 1959 - March 26, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - March 27, 1960 - June 3, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - June 3, 1960 - December 28, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - December 29, 1960 - April 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - April 10, 1961 - June 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - June 22, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 204)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 205)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 208)
  - November 14, 1961 - February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 209)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 212)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 214)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 216)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 219)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 220)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 221)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 222)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 223)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 224)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 225)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 226)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 227)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - February 14, 1962 - May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 229)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 230)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 232)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 233)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - May 21, 1962 - October 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 251)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 252)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 253)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 254)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 255)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 264)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 265)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 266)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 270)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 272)
  - October 7, 1962 - February 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 273)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 274)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 280)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 281)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 286)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 289)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 290)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 291)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 292)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 294)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 295)
  - March 1, 1963 - June 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 297)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 298)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 299)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 301)